Hi
I'm here at the airport in Portland about 50 cities into what is going to be a hundred city tour
It's going exceptionally well
Audiences in each city and the people I've met afterward have been very enthusiastic
There seems to be a rapidly developing market for relatively long-form intellectual discourse
Driven by YouTube and podcasts which have none of the bandwidth limitations of traditional media forms
I just had two evenings of productive discussion with Sam Harris in Vancouver
I'm going to post my notes from those talks on my blog at Jordan B Peterson dot.com
We talked about the relationship between facts and values and the role that narrative and story might play in bringing the two together
for better or worse
The Vancouver events sold out
The next discussion with Sam, the third, which will also feature Douglas Murray
Will take place in Dublin Ireland on the 14th of July at the three Arena
Followed by the final fourth discussion at the o2 arena in London on the 16th
Tickets for those discussions are still available. You can find them at the events page on my website
That's Jordan B Peterson com or in the written description of this video below
All the discussions with Sam are being filmed
And will be released in video and podcast form within the next few months after the remaining two discussions in Dublin and London
Because of the positive response from audiences and from individual audience members
I've added another 19 cities to the 12 rules tour these include Rochester, Westbury Wallingford
Baltimore Durham Miami Orlando st. Petersburg and Jacksonville
Cincinnati and Cleveland Grand Rapids Des Moines st. Louis, Kansas City, Denver
Colorado Springs, San Antonio and Irving
You can get presale tickets using the code doctor jbp until Thursday
June 28 at 10 p.m. Tickets go on sale everyone Friday, June 29th at 10 a.m
I'm also touring Canada in July and August
dates locations and ticket links are also listed below in the video description and
available at jordan b peterson dot.com
Finally i'll be speaking in about a dozen cities in Europe in October in November and Australia in February
Those venues and dates will be announced in the next few weeks
Thanks for watching or listening
I'm looking forward to seeing you potentially at one of these lectures
Bye for now from Portland